Hello friends, today we are again present in front of you after waking up at
9:00 in the morning, Allah,
today's first question is here for you,
I am Pranav Singh Thakur, now we are
in the middle and our Bhupati Adha, which
we have started with ICICI Lombard, this
Road Safety Online Road Safety
Quiz Contest, we got a lot of
love from you all and many people have
certified us, so
first of all I want to
thank you very much to the Indian public on behalf of all our team for
joining us, now
till date I
want to present before you the first Khusro question,
you have to read it carefully and
participate with us in it, so friends,
today's first question of the morning which is going to be
liked in the next 2 hours is that your
shopping is Grocery Sinha, Roland,
Bill Pass, Kinnars, Park in front of
Bishop Park in designated all places at a
distance, no parking, I am reading it again,
this question is before you on your
shopping  Groceries in a row in this you will way the
answer is its first parking is
Rahul Beach is park in front of President's
Park in designated park place at a
distance of ardi is arcade no parking
for my Hindi speaking people I am
tweeting this in Hindi also Akbar is the
question is that you are going to
shop for goods at your home on a broken road there will be a row in this
and you have to park so
what will you do you have four options
which one do you think is the best option for you
9th is to park in the row of this you were
going in a line you will cut the fog in a way
gather shop you had to buy goods from a shop
you will cover that medico in front of that shop
and the unknown front
point says that you have to go to the
designated place for parking
where to make this place for parking
now when will you come there and park your car
then you will do the full propagation on  If it is there then you should
not add salt. Now we will talk to it there. So
friends, these are four questions. There are 14
answers to the first question. Mother's complaint.
Now take four places on it. You should think and ponder over it
and answer it. You will get this new video of ours
on our website India and India will
progress to edit. You will also get
it live on Facebook. You can go and give your correct
answer and participate in your searches with us. Apart from this,
within the next whole day you will get four more
questions. As I had said yesterday also, at
7 o'clock, this question will come. This question is about a birthday
or these questions. At 2005 in the evening,
we will bring the fifth question in front of you. The
time for answering those five questions will be till 7 o'clock
and after 7 o'clock, it will be closed
for today. The
people who have used the correct answers to these two questions will get it.
Both of them will get it on this temple and we will add it to
our online TV show Rafael,
Online Girls Painting. We will
release the names of the winners there on the same day at the same time.
We will announce the names of three lucky winners for each question.
And as I have also told friends.
You tell me that the rule is that if more than one
person answers a question correctly,
then we will announce the names of three lucky winners through lottery only
and they can get an exciting chance to
win related to our road, so friends,
read about them and I will bring you the opportunity to
join us, subscribe to the alarm,
play online quiz contest and
win prizes, there are 15 lucky winners every day, the
winners of the first five questions will
get press every day, so friends, you should
not miss this opportunity at all and I
would like to thank our sponsors, this program is being sponsored by such Lombards
whose people have
Protect Your Family with this, a
lot of them must have taken
advantage of such Lumba's Dhani Foreign Policy, it must be
helping you and even then,
in an emergency situation, you would need it in your emergency separation, so
for that, we
also thank our sponsors very much for having sponsored
our  We chose this program
and made it with us,
in the conclusion of which we are present among you, so
friends, today we were talking about
road safety in Hathin in
general, and if you must have
seen in that, we had two guests,
Sharad is the Chairman of Bullet Research Institute, Automotive
Skill Development Council and Jogendra
Singh Rathore is the District Transport Officer
under the Rajasthan Transport Department,
when we talked to both of them, some main
points came out of them, friends, I would
definitely like to discuss them with you here
again,
and first of all, when
we were talking for five minutes, then in this Tikki, the statistics of road accidents of the Government of India, in
most of the accidents,
we talk about it and there is a little foolishness of the driver
or we can call it negligence, this
skill should be developed to drive the vehicle
in a different environment because the road environment,
friends, never remains the same, it always keeps
changing, the weather also keeps changing and we have to
drive on it, and so,
I have but a few complaints registered here from the
taxi driver.  Drivers travel long distances
and transport goods for us, they transport
passengers from one place to another within a
stated time of 1 hour.
Their Tukaram is
not the only support of their wives, their driving is their profession. So
friends,
they cover so many states in a single trip. For example, I have to go
from Jaipur to Delhi.
I am in Jaipur and am going to Delhi. So,
Jaipur, Rajasthan, Haryana and Delhi are
SA 380. There are not only skin problems
and the difference is only in the terms of the
fare for driving to the road. If you take Rajasthan, you will make
them unrighteous and innocent towards development. The heat will
start from 1st April and the
temperature will
increase further and as you move above Delhi
towards Uttarakhand or Kashmir or towards
Himachal like Shimla, the
weather becomes cold there. At the same
time, if you are 300 meters below the DEO
like Jaipur, then
if you come to the desert of Rajasthan in May-June, its
heat will be for you for half a minute
and from there itself, if you go
up like 10 kilometers
towards Shimla,  It happened that we went to Kullu Manali
and Rich and I wanted to go for a summer vacation from our spot city. At
that
time, whoever took us there every day, on the
support of Aamir, Rajasthan, I will
talk to the roadways channel. Private builders
and bus drivers are there daily for them from Jaipur to
Kullu Manali. Now Tanu, if our
boat is taking us from Jaipur to celebrate
or taking a male deer, you don't have to go there, it takes
12 hours to reach
Manali. Western influence, think about the
temperature
clock in May, when we leave for Jaipur, the
temperature is 100 degrees and we
reach there. The next morning, if the sun
panel gets damaged, then there is a
temperature of 5 degrees and the temperature is
40 to 45 degrees.
After greeting our brothers,
diseases spread from there. Then from there we
come back in the heat. Then we go back from here. There are
officers and they get trimmed every morning
and have to bear the difference of acting heat
and during that time, we also have to drive the vehicle for
12 hours and road behavior
arm hole.  They have to decide, so
friends, this pass is not
for us, now we carry our small and big names on
motorcycles, the government has given us some
money for it and because I have
15 years of
experience in general with
big trucks, but on this road, there are a few
trains for 100 rupees, that is
after a specific month of training and they have a lot of road experience, so the person in
charge of driving the vehicle
says that he is comparatively
less hasty, in comparison to us people who fight with small vehicles,
number two wheelers,
because we do not react to such temperature every day,
we just drive for a
kilometer in our own soil, our own area, we
come and go every day and we
live in the same temperature and we drive for only
half an hour, one and a half inch maximum, that is, if there is
entry in one of our vehicles and any other work of yours is included there,
you have to do that much exercise to reach there,
after that you go inside your comfortable room
You enter your office comfortably and do
your work, then in the evening you leave, just
think how little we type
and those of us who drive
near the pimps and heavy vehicles and truck
drivers do so much work
and how much the screen temperatures
go through every day, on the night of Shubh and Labh, a
text in temperature in the heat and
in the soft section, I go back to the office in the heat,
so how much spray on the body of the china they have to
bear and during that time we two
wheeler and government people make such
mistakes that we overdo it anywhere, we do
not keep the small road incomplete,
we go near the leaf, then
we stop the vehicle by applying brakes anywhere and they face a
lot of difficulty in handling their vehicle because it is a heavy
vehicle, friends and they are
not able to stop the vehicle by applying brakes suddenly, the
mental strain of their dog body,
I have planned something that it should
not affect their body physically in so much money,
front and internally, their first digital
drop by drop all the changes keep happening
100 grams and in that mental state we
need to be a little bit in touch and
for this you are requested
again and again that whenever you see a big vehicle
or a bus or even other
vehicles, keep a little bit of distance and
drive by controlling your speed a little bit so that
you have to apply brakes or if
a person comes in front of you with a knife, then
you should maintain a little bit of distance with him, if you feel
restrained by doing this then you should keep yourself
in a safe work place, so friends
my message to you today is that
we should control ourselves and keep our distance
and we are moving cautiously from any vehicle,
generally avoid big vehicles, heavy
vehicles, trucks, petrol and tempo,
you people on motorcycles and the bad
drivers should drive by keeping a little bit of distance
and if 1 minute is
completed, whether it is 2 seconds or 3 seconds, the foot will
remain between the feet, if the captains have to
apply brakes then you should not go and hit him and if you want to shoot
then friends this is my message
for you today, now I am  The first
question is being posted today,
answer it and ensure your participation with us.
You can be a lucky winner. I
am your name, it was in the evening and
you get the prize, then that match question will be
valid again. You are shopping on
grocery day airplane, you well as
our right these days is roll beach, park in
front of the president, on Kinnar David
and place and third tips on digwat no
point in Hindi, you are going to any active
shopping to
buy some stuff for your home and
all your things are on the road, then you will do your answer in a topic located
joint, that is, you have to
stop your car right here,
second is that
you have to pick up the stuff from the shop and
park your vehicle right in front of that shop,
third is that if the road is a
little far away, then go out and
park your car and it
comes five times when both the cuttings which have been
marked on the city touch and you will
park your car on the no.  Friends, you will
also answer and right now I will
put this question online for the next 2 hours, now you can participate in it,
my second question is Hero Kam
got a new Hunter, I will be with you,
she will tell you what the second question is and
similarly
we will give you the proof that we have by 5 o'clock and you
give us the answer on that in the next 2 hours and we will try to give the correct
answer at 10 pm
on Quentin Somerville online store,
we will try in that, the names of the lucky 15 winners will
also be announced and they will
get prizes, so pick up fast typing
and how much do you know on Inter College Road
and if there is also a chance to practice
your rhythm of dancing then it is a very
situation, so come with us, I will ask you for
your heart, at what time will you go out
on the road, stay safe and take care of yourself,
this is a
jiffy